Ocean man, take me by the hand
Lead me to the land that you understand
Ocean man, the voyage to the corner of the globe
Is a real trip
Ocean man, the crust of a tan man imbibed by the sand
Soaking up the thirst of the land

Ocean man, can you see through the wonder of amazement
At the Oberman
Ocean man, the crust is elusive when it casts forth
To the childlike man
Ocean man, the sequence of a life form braised in the sand
Soaking up the thirst of the land